One day I realised it:
The cruel reality which lies dormant within the peaceful world.
The pain of the person I've always loved.
My father and mother, and everyone in that house...
...they don't love that person.
Far from it.
They don't object to tormenting him even more.
And that's why I...
Hagun Academy Entrance & Opening Ceremony
Good job, Stella-san.
It's Stella!
Ah...
Well then, Stella, you know...
What?
I run twenty kilometres every day out of habit,
but you don't have to push yourself to keep up.
I'm fine with this much.
But you know, you have potent magic which compensates for your physical ability...
It's okay!
I finished just fine today, didn't I?
You really are pretty competitive, aren't you, Stella?
Here.
Isn't that...
A sports drink.
I mean...
...an indirect kiss.
You don't want it because my lips touched it, right?
Sorry.
I-I didn't say I don't want it!
If anything, the other way around.
Huh?
Wh-Whatever,
just give it to me!
You seem pretty happy.
Yeah.
My little sister enrols today.
We haven't met in four years.
Huh?
Hey, that little sister of yours...
...she's not a non-blood-related sister or anything, is she?
No, she's a perfectly normal blood-related sibling.
In that case, it's all right.
What did you approve of just now?
Voi ținti sus, spre o lume nouă și curajoasă
Cu vârful unei săbii a pasiunii
Ceea ce însemnez în acest loc este sufletul meu
Nu voi lăsa pe nimeni să-mi atingă identitatea
Bătăile inimii încep să rezoneze
Destinul meu va fi decis în acest moment
Fii arogant și râzi de determinarea mea
Îmi voi alunga îndoiala și voi continua să înaintez
Vom înainta fără a privi înapoi
De asta o voi distruge chiar acum
Da, la ușa grea care blochează drumul spre viitor mă refer
Folosește-ți toată puterea și mintea ascuțită
până în ultima clipă
Distruge-o dintr-o singură lovitură
Da, la ușa grea care nu te lasă să mergi spre viitor mă refer
Reînvie, momentul a venit
Acesta este punctul culminant
E momentul nostru să fim pe primul loc
All new students, congratulations on your enrolment!
I'm your homeroom teacher, Oreki Yuuri.
I'm a young, newbie teacher,
and this is my first homeroom class.
Cavalerul repetent II
Please call me Yuri-chan.
You don't have classes today...
What a worn-out teacher.
Well, yeah.
But she's a good teacher.
Everybody, you remember what Chairman-sensei said at the entrance ceremony, don't you?
Until last year, our school's representatives were selected by ability points.
But starting this year, all students will be
participating in combat selection.
From among the winners, the top six
will become representatives.
It's a simple and fair way to do it.
And so, the intra-school battles will start next week.
Intra-school battles start next week
Match schedule
The match schedule and opponents will be sent to your student notebooks via e-mail.
.
Opponents
delivered to student notebooks
by
e-mail
Be sure to check the details.
Check
important details!
Sensei!
No, no!
Yuri
Y
u
r
i
Yuri
chan
c
h
a
n
chan
If you don't call me Yuri-chan, I won't answer you!
Y-Yuri-chan.
Yes, what is it, Stella-chan?
Yuri
Y
u
r
i
Yuri
chan
c
h
a
n
chan
How many matches will there be in total?
Hm...
There will be easily more than ten matches per person.
You're best off preparing to have one match every three days.
Huh, for real?
What a pain.
Once every three days.
If that's the case, Ittou Shura...
Those who don't want to do it can abstain.
It doesn't affect your grades.
However, I think it's a wonderful thing that everybody has an equal chance.
So try your best, by all means.
All right, everybody,
All Our Might
let's do our best with all our might this year!
Okay, everybody together!
Yeah, yeah, y-
All Our Might
Y-Yuri-chan?!
Ah, I knew it.
Actually, I vomit a litre of blood every day.
Th-That's bad.
Don't push yourself too hard, Sensei.
Yeah.
But you know, it's a special day.
I thought looking unhealthy wouldn't cut it.
I was able to enrol here because Sensei approved of it.
But that was because of your abilities, even in spite of the unfortunate things that happened last year.
Hey,
your last year was unfortunate?
Ah, you know,
it's about how I couldn't participate in classes.
Before I enrolled, there were no criteria for ability points.
What do you mean-
Kurogane-senpai!
I can finally talk with you, Senpai!
Wh-What are you doing, Ikki?!
I'm wondering that myself!
Who are you?
I'm Kusakabe Kagami, from the same class as you!
Senpai, I'm a huge fan of yours!
Huh, fan?
I happened to see the mock battle earlier.
You're pretty strong, aren't you?
W-Well, not really...
You know, I'm thinking about starting a newspaper club.
And I want you to adorn the memorable first issue!
Please let me feature you!
I-I'm not really that impressive...
How nice for you, to be this popular right at the start of the new term.
How about you just give in and let her feature you, Senpai?
Stella!
I already know the headline too!
"Kurogane Ikki the Prodigy Surprises: Beats the Legendary Genius Knight"!
How about that?
U-Uh...
Let's talk about this again later.
Hey, Stella!
Finally, I found you.
Shizuku...
Hey, isn't that...
It's Lorelei.
The new student whose results-
It's been a while,
Onii-sama.
Shizuku!
I didn't notice you.
I was thinking of coming to see you later.
Sorry you had to find me.
It's fine, I just couldn't wait.
Onii-sama!
Wh-What's going on?!
What a scoop!
I wanted to see you all this time.
Shizuku...
H-Hey, Ikki...
Wh-What are you doing?!
I-I don't know myself!
It's a kiss, of course.
A kiss is a sign of deep affection.
Men and women with the
shallow ties of lovers do it.
So, based on that, it's only natural that a brother and sister,
bound by much deeper ties, do it too.
In some countries, it's akin to a greeting.
Is that so?
Siblings don't kiss like that in my country!
I don't think other countries do either.
It's as they say.
They're them, and we're us.
Remembering those four years of longing,
even us sleeping together would be no more than a greeting.
As if!
Shizuku, a girl shouldn't say things like that!
I'm just joking.
But Onii-sama, if you were to wish for it-
No!
Pull yourself together, Ikki!
Why are you acting like this is natural?
Th-Thanks for moving her, Stella.
So you're the legendary Princess Stella?
Why are you interfering in the sibling-to-sibling communication of us commoners?
As if that kind of manipulation is any kind of communication!
That's for Onii-sama and me to decide.
You have nothing to do with it.
If you understand, countryside princess, you should just shut up.
I-It does have something to do with me!
Huh, and what is that?
W-Well, Ikki is...
What do you have to do with it?
Ikki is my master,
and I'm his servant!
H-Hey, Stella!
Let's forget about that already-
A huge scandal!
The first issue's headline:
"Struggle in my arms:
the savage roommate, the slave princess,
and their indecent 72 hours in a locked room"!
Struggle in my arms:
the savage roommate, the slave princess
and their indecent
72 hours  in a locked
room
and their indecent
72 hours  in a locked
room
and their indecent
72 hours  in a locked
room
That's too long!
Plus, it's a misunderstanding anyway.
It's not a misunderstanding.
In exchange for winning the duel,
you gave me an order, didn't you?
Stella, sleep in the same bed with me.
Who's that cool guy?!
And it didn't have that immoral tension either!
Is that true?
Onii-sama, I'm asking whether it's true.
Um, well, I guess it's kind of true.
But it's a bunk bed...
I see.
It's true, huh?
U-Um...
Shizuku-san?
Shizuku is going to set Onii-sama free now.
Splash, Yoishigure.
Shizuku, don't do that!
It's fine, Onii-sama.
My affinity is water.
I can kill Stella-san and her flame affinity.
That's not what I'm saying!
If you use your device in a place like this...
Serve me, Laevateinn!
Huh?
Why do you want to do this too, Stella?!
Quite a modest device you have there.
Just like your chest.
And you too,
a woman with a graceless chest has a graceless device.
They're both unnecessarily big.
Hey, now,
I can't cope with listening to the jealousy of someone lacking in both chest and soul.
Fatty.
Hag.
Drop dead!
Inside or outside of school,
it's forbidden to deploy your devices outside of allowed areas.
You should be punished with house arrest,
but considering it's still the first day,
I decided on a week of toilet cleaning.
You should be thankful for my leniency.
Thank you very much, Chairman-sensei.
I will reflect upon my actions, and I won't do it again.
Good.
You can go home after cleaning all the girls' toilets within the school.
By the way, there are 27 of them.
Washboard.
Advertising balloon.
Like a child.
Bigger than a MILF.
Leaky bucket!
Firecracker!
Zero metres above sea level.
Mt. Everest.
Torn, flat water pillow.
Overinflated blow-up doll!
Hagun Academy Student Dormitory
I-I'm letting you off for today!
So you're admitting defeat?
Please never get near Onii-sama again.
I'm not admitting anything!
And too bad for you,
but I can't not get near him.
We're roommates, after all.
Well, no matter what you do with that lewd body of yours,
Onii-sama belongs to me.
Don't be stupid!
Isn't it lewd for a little sister by blood to do such things to her brother?
Some things can only be understood by blood relatives.
Like what, for example?
Go ahead and explain it.
Well...
Yes?
No matter what it is, you'll never understand Onii-sama's feelings!
You, who's not even part
of the Kurogane family-
Don't suddenly make it about family!
I wouldn't be so sure about that!
So you do understand?
How my brother feels after always being treated like he doesn't exist?!
Huh?
What do you mean?
What do you mean, "like he doesn't exist"?
It has nothing to do with you.
There's nothing you can do.
Oh, welcome.
I finally get to meet my roommate.
I was worried because you weren't showing up.
I'm Arisuin Nagi.
My friends call me Alice.
Hagun Academy Student Dormitory
What did she mean, "like he doesn't exist"?
Huh, Stella?
Why are you here?
U-Um...
I was waiting for you.
I thought we could practice together, but you weren't there.
Ah, I thought you'd probably be tired today.
Sorry.
Well, it's fine.
Here.
You forgot this, didn't you?
Ah, thank you.
Ikki.
Ikki, were you ever treated like you didn't exist?
Ah, sorry!
I didn't mean to be so forward about this...
Um, did you perhaps hear that from Shizuku?
Y-Yeah.
Just a bit.
I see.
But that's good timing.
I meant to talk to you about that eventually anyway.
Oh?
It's pretty depressing, but will you hear my story?
Yeah.
Stella, do you know Samurai Ryouma?
Of course I do!
The hero who guided Japan to victory in the past great war.
His real name is Ryouma Kurogane.
Oh.
That's right; he's my great-grandfather.
And he's also the person I'm aiming to become.
Generation after generation, the Kurogane family has produced excellent Blazers.
We're what you'd call a distinguished family.
But I had no talent, so my parents and relatives always treated me like I didn't exist.
Family gatherings never included a seat for me.
I heard those voices - of people having fun.
One year, at the New Year's party,
I simply couldn't take it any more.
I had nowhere to go.
I just couldn't be in that house.
However...
Before I knew it, the weather turned rough, and I got lost.
I was preparing to die already.
That's when I just kept thinking...
...how frustrating it was that this was my end.
That's when he appeared before me.
Samurai Ryouma?
Yeah.
I remember word-for-word what he said to me back then.
"Are you annoyed, youngster?"
"Don't throw away that frustration just because you're the weakest."
That's proof that you haven't given up yet.
On yourself, that is.
Got it, boy?
Don't become a worthless man who has given up and says that they're living within their means.
A person can do anything if they refuse to give up.
After all, we're creatures without wings, and yet we've gone to the moon.
Although they were just words,
they truly did save me.
So that's when I decided
that I'd become an adult like him.
That if I ever come across someone in the same situation,
I'd become a person who can pass along his words.
But to do that,
I'll have to become strong myself.
Strong like him.
So that's why you want to become a knight?
But nobody would teach me anything,
so I always trained alone.
Alone...
And then, I managed to enrol in this academy.
But it seems the Kurogane family are troubled that a failure like me could become a knight.
They've coerced the school.
Ability criteria for attending classes.
Those are something the academy's then-chairman created...
...so that I couldn't graduate.
Fortunately, Shinguuji-sensei became the chairman.
But I still think that type of harassment will continue.
But even so...
You won't give up,
even if you get badly burnt.
Right?
I remember those kinds of feelings too.
I see.
Of course you would.
But Ikki, there's one correction I'd like to request.
What?
You said this morning that I'm competitive, didn't you?
Yeah...
Got it, I'll correct that.
We're both competitive.
Exactly!
I loved my dear big brother
and kept loving him even after he left home.
But one day I realised how badly the family treated him.
I detested those people from the bottom of my heart.
And that's when I decided.
Father's love, mother's love,
big brother's love, little sister's love...
I'd provide them all to my brother myself.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm rambling on, even though we just met.
Shizuku, you hate people, don't you?
Huh?
You may have been shy with strangers to begin with,
but maybe in your case, your relationship with your family made it worse.
I understand.
I used to know a similar girl.
Well, we're going to know each other for a while,
so if you ever need to talk, you can talk to me.
Think of me as your big sister.
On/Off
Bath Auto
Ikki, I'm coming in.
Sure, come on in.
Wait!
Hey, S-Stella!
Wh-What now?
It shouldn't be that shocking.
Of course...
Of course I'd be shocked!
What's up?!
U-Um...
I-I thought I'd wash you.
Huh?
Wh-Why?!
Well, that's...
I'm your servant, aren't I?
Doing this is just natural-
or rather, my duty!
Yeah.
No, no!
I didn't even ask for it!
A first-class servant does it without being asked!
So sit down already.
B-But...
I'll boil you.
O-Okay.
All right, your back is next.
S-Sure.
Hey, Ikki.
Ikki, do you, um...
Wh-What?
...like girls' chests and such?
Wh-What's that all of a sudden?!
You looked happy about being pressed between that Kagami girl's,
and you've been looking at mine too for a while now...
I-I'm sorry!
There's no need to apologise.
How are they?
Do you like them?
I like them.
Th-This feeling...
No, they'll rub!
Wh-What?!
N-Nu te mișca!
B-Bine!
Nu te mai mișca!
H-Hey, Stella, isn't it time to-
Nu te uita!
Stella!
Y-You're touching me right now...
...b-bare?
Nu!
Failed         Knight